careerage.com 2019-05-10

# CareerAge.com Privacy Policy

  1. **Overview**

CareerAge.com and its associate websites are committed to respecting the privacy of our users. We strive to provide a safe, secure user experience. This Privacy Statement sets forth the online data collection and usage policies and practices that apply to the CareerAge.com Web Sites (sometimes referred to herein as the "CareerAge.com Sites") and does not apply to information we collect in any other fashion. 

Your data will be stored and processed in whole or in part on the servers located anywhere in the world. The information we gather on the CareerAge.com Sites may be shared within the CareerAge-affiliated companies on a worldwide basis in order to deliver the products and services we offer to employers such as searches for job seekers or in order to undertake analysis of our database such as aggregate profiling of our registered users. "Affiliated companies" means entities that control, are controlled by or are under common control with CareerAge.com. 

The CareerAge.com Sites contain links to other Web sites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites to which you choose to link from our Sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those other Web sites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information. 

  2. **Collection and Use of Information by CareerAge.com**

In some areas of CareerAge.com, we request or may request that you provide personal information, including your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, contact information, billing information and any other information from which your identity is discernible. In other areas, we collect or may collect demographic information that is not unique to you such as your age, preferences, gender, interests and favorites. Sometimes we collect or may collect a combination of the two types of information. Examples of areas on the CareerAge.com Sites where we collect personal or combined personal and demographic data are pages where you can open a CareerAge.com account, sign up to use a service, post a resume or purchase a product. 

In addition, we may indirectly collect information about you when you use certain third party services available on CareerAge.com. For example, if you register on CareerAge.com by using your OpenID, such information will be subject to, and treated in accordance with, the policies and practices described in this Privacy Statement. 

We may also gather or may not gather certain information about your use of CareerAge.com, such as what areas you visit and what services you access. Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by us. This information can include without limitation your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses, but is not linked to your personal information. 

We may sometimes present you the opportunity to provide descriptive, cultural, preferential and/or life style information about yourself, but it is solely up to you whether you furnish such information. If you do provide such information, you are thereby consenting to the use of that information in accordance with the policies and practices described in this Privacy Statement. For example, such information may be used for the purpose of determining your potential interest in receiving e-mail or other communications about particular products or services. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about the CareerAge.com Sites or refer a job posting to a friend, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the CareerAge.com Sites or view the job posting. We may store this information to invite them to use CareerAge.com services in future. 

  3. **Our Use of Your Information**

We use the information we gather on CareerAge.com, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving the CareerAge.com Sites, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that we offer. 

If you have provided consent for us to do so, we may also use the information we gather to inform you of other products or services available from us or our affiliated companies or to contact you about your opinion of current products and services or potential new products and services that may be offered. 

We may use your contact information in order to send you e-mail or other communications regarding updates at the CareerAge.com Sites or if we have any new information, service, article or job postings etc. which we think that it may be of interest to you. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you. 

In addition, you shall be given the option to elect or not elect to receive additional communications, information and promotions, including without limitation, free informational newsletters from us relating to topics that may be of special interest to you, such as career management advice, as and when it is offered. 

We have areas on the CareerAge.com Sites where you can submit feedback. Any feedback you submit in these areas becomes our property, and we can use such feedback (such as success stories) for marketing purposes or to contact you for further information. 

  4. **Choices Regarding the Disclosure of Personal Information to Others**
    1. We disclose information to companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include hosting our Web servers, data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party. 
    2. We disclose information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public. 
    3. We disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event we become the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. You will be notified of sale of all or a substantial portion of our business to a third party via email or through a prominent notice posted on the CareerAge.com Sites. 
  5. **Other Uses of Information**

We may share aggregated anonymous information about visitors to CareerAge.com (for example, the number of visitors to CareerAge.com's job search area) with its clients, partners and other third parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the CareerAge.com Sites and how those visitors use the CareerAge.com Sites. 

We may supply technology, hosting and related services to other leading companies to power recruitment areas on their Web sites (sometimes referred to as "Hosted Career Sites"). Personal and/or demographic information supplied by you in Hosted Career Sites becomes part of the CareerAge.com database, but it is not accessible by anyone other than you, CareerAge.com and the company concerned without your consent. If you attempt to register with CareerAge.com after registering with a Hosted Career Site, CareerAge.com will recognize your information and you will be able to use the information you provided to the Hosted Career Site in your account registration. 

Information gathered on a page in a Hosted Career Site or on a co-branded page (such as that of a contest co-sponsored by CareerAge.com and another company), may become the property of the other company or of both us and the other company. In that instance, the use of such information by the other company will be subject to the privacy policy of that company. We are not responsible for that company's use of your personal or demographic information. 

If you apply for a position on CareerAge.com or through a Hosted Career Site, you may be asked to provide information on your gender, race or other protected status where permitted by applicable law. Some employers are required by law to gather this information from job applicants for reporting and record-keeping requirements. You should understand that if provided, this information will be used by employers only in accordance with applicable law and will not be used in making any negative employment decisions. All information provided will be kept separate from your expression of interest in any job opportunity. Providing this information is strictly voluntary and you will not be subject to any adverse action or treatment if you choose not to provide this information. 

  6. **Personal Information on Resumes and Profiles**

Since CareerAge.com is a career site, we give you three options regarding the accessibility of your resume: 

    1. You can store your resume in our database, but not allow it to be searchable by potential employers. Not allowing your resume to be searchable means that you can use it to apply for a job online, but employers and recruiters will not have access to search it through our resume database product. 
    2. If you allow your resume to be searchable without making it confidential and hiding your contact information, then all parties with access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) will have access to your resume. 
    3. If you have a confidential resume, but apply to a job posting on CareerAge.com, the employer to whom you send your resume will be able to view your contact information. 

We attempt to limit access to our searchable resume database (or copies thereof) only to paying employers, recruiters, hiring managers, and human resource professionals, as well as law enforcement and national security agencies, but cannot guarantee that other parties will not gain access to this database. We are not responsible for the use made of resumes by third parties who access such resumes while they are in our searchable database. You may remove your resume on CareerAge.com at anytime, but, employers, recruiters and others who have paid for access to the CareerAge.com resume database or to obtain a copy of that database as well as parties who have otherwise gained access may have retained a copy of your resume in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of resumes or profiles in these instances. 

  7. **Posting to Public Areas of CareerAge.com**

Please remember that if you post any of your personal information in public areas of CareerAge.com such as in online forums or chat rooms, or in the CareerAge.com searchable resume database, such information may be collected and used by others over whom we have no control. We are not responsible for the use made by third parties of information you post or otherwise make available in public areas of CareerAge.com or CareerAge.com Networking. 

  8. **Use of Cookies**

We use "cookies" to help personalize and maximize your online experience and time online. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize CareerAge.com pages, or register for services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. When you return to CareerAge.com, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized. We also use cookies to track click streams and for load balancing. 

You may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline all cookies if you prefer. Alternatively, you may be able to modify your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to decline cookies, however, that may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on CareerAge.com. 

    * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on CareerAge.com 
    * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to CareerAge.com and other sites on the Internet. 
    * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
  9. **Third-party Advertising Companies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

  10. **Use of Web Beacons**

CareerAge.com Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs). 

  11. **Access to and Modification of Your Information**

You may review, correct, update or change your account information at any time. 

To change your account information, simply log into your account, go to your Account Profile, review your account information and, if you wish, edit it with the options provided. 

If you opted to receive newsletters, commercial e-mails or other communications from CareerAge.com or third parties at the time you created an account, but subsequently changed your mind, you may opt-out by editing your Account Profile as described above. If you previously opted not to receive such communications, you may later opt-in by editing your Account Profile as well. 

We retain indefinitely all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use of CareerAge.com more efficient, practical, and relevant. Of course, you can delete your resume from CareerAge.com's online database, close your account at any time (by writing to us at support@CareerAge.com) in which event we will remove all our copies of your resume from CareerAge.com, your account information except for an archival copy which is not accessible on the Internet. 

  12. **Security of the Personal Information**

We have implemented commercially reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. 

When you place an order online at CareerAge.com your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted or stolen while being transmitted. We use a service company to process its credit card transactions. For further information on this company's privacy and security practices, please http://www.ccavenues.com and http://www.Paypal.com 

  13. **Children**

The CareerAge.com Sites are not intended for children under 18 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18. 

  14. **Changes to Privacy Statement**

If we decide to materially change our Privacy Statement for CareerAge.com, we will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. 

If at any time, you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Statement or believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Statement, please feel free to email us at support@careerage.com. We will use reasonable efforts to promptly answer your question or resolve your problem.
